# REX MACAPINLAC

#### Digital Media Specialist I UI Designer

I am a jack-of-all-trades content creator. I bear 7+ years of experience in website and social media management, graphic design, video editing, and UX. I am still ever-passionate in helping brands visually define their identity, services, and strengths, as a newly certified UI Designer through CareerFoundry.

### CONTACT

**Phone** (508) 271-5561

Email rexmacofficial@gmail.com

**Current Location**Boston, MA

## **EDUCATION**

2023

**UI Design Program**CareerFoundry

**UX Foundations**General Assembly

**B.A., Communications**Stonehill College I Easton, MA

#### **EXPERTISE**

- UI/UX
- Visual Design
- Website Management (Wordpress; Drupal)
- Video Editing (Premiere)
- Graphic Design
- Copywriting
- Text Animation

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2023 - Present

Mass Commission for the Deaf & Hard of Hearing | Boston, MA Social Media & Digital Content Specialist

- Create accessible video and graphic design content to promote State services for the deaf and hard of hearing
- Manage website and social media content in adherence with Commission's standards for compliance and accessibility
- · Develop and execute strategy to grow following across digital platforms

2021 - 2023

Franciscan Children's | Boston, MA Digital Specialist (2021-2023)

- Managed hospital website's daily operations and redesign in direct collaboration with CEO and Senior Leadership team
- Designed graphics for hospital and school social media channels, enewsletters, print advertisements, brochures, campus displays, and event signage
- Produced photos, video, and animated content for digital advertising campaigns and hospital news monitors

2017 - 2021

Bay State Savings Bank | Worcester, MA 01608 AVP (2021) | Marketing Officer (2019-2021) | Marketing Assistant (2017-2019)

- Created design, video, and written content for digital, print, radio, and billboard advertising campaigns
- Managed digital media including Bank website, social media, online banking platform, and mobile app
- Oversaw relationships, strategy, distribution, and budget with media vendors
- Designed and wrote copy for Bank newsletters, annual reports, brochures, press releases, and mailers
- Executed multiple geotargeted display, SEM, and email advertising campaigns which earned the Bank over \$2.9M in 2020

## RELEVANT PROFICIENCIES

Wordpress | Invision | Slack | Adobe Photoshop, Indesign, Lightroom, and Premiere | Microsoft Word, Powerpoint, Excel, and Outlook | Google Analytics and Google My Business MailChimp | Figma | Facebook | Twitter | Instagram | Hootsuite